

MakMendelson

Contact



443 854 0819



mak.mendelson (at) gmail.com



forekast.github.io



twitter.com/AltF4WillHelp



linkedin.com/in/makmendelson

Skills

- User Interface Design
- User Experience Design
- User Experience Testing
- Product Development
- **▶** Game Development
- Adobe Illustrator
- **▶** Game Design
- Logo Design & Branding
- Business Cards & Stationary
- Adobe Photoshop
- Digital Painting
- ▶ Concept Art
- **▶** Blender
- ▶ 2D & 3D Animation
- ▶ Texturing
- Fine Art

Languages

- **English**
- Russian
- Spanish

Summary

I co-founded, managed, and developed products at a **start-up** video game company for four years. It was an invaluable experience, and, given the chance, I'd absolutely do it again with what I know now.

I've since spent a couple years away from the Games Industry, **developing skills** in User Interface & Experience Design, as well as Testing, as an employee at a Government Contractor.

I'm currently looking for a position where I can further develop easy-to-use and visually appealing User Experiences, create game art, or otherwise take part in **creative design and development** with an experienced team.

I look forward to meeting you!

Experience

User Interface Consultant and Tester

December 2014 - Present

Buchanan & Edwards

http://buchanan-edwards.com/

- \cdot Consulted, generated high-fidelity mock-ups, and tested User Interfaces in the development of a Knowledge Management Tool web application for the Department of State
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Collaborated with Business Analysts to collect, define, and document client requirements
- \cdot Collaborated with Developers to determine best implementation strategies, and to ensure product is inline with current design mock-ups
- · Developed Branding and Stationary
- · I currently hold and active DOD SECRET clearance

Co-Founder and Visual Artist

April 2010 - February 2014

Gradient Studios, LLC.

http://www.gradientstudios.com

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Co-founded Gradient Studios, LLC. right out of college
- · Lead Artis
- · Developed Start-to-Finish, and Shipped two games of our own Intellectual Property
- · Determined and Designed aesthetics for several games
- · Created UI and game assets for several games
- · Created promotional material: trailer/gameplay videos, posters, booth design
- · Took part in securing seed funding from Accomplice (formerly of Altas Ventures)

Helpdesk Consultant

August 2006 — May 2010

Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute

http://rpi.edu/

· Provided Software at the Computer Center to Students, Faculty, and Staff

Education

Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute

2006 - 2010

BS, Games & Simulation Arts & Sciences, Concentration in Electronic Arts

Gilman School 2002-2006

High School Diploma